Find where you belong.
News of the World is a drama, western, adventure
film directed by Paul Greengrass.
A Texan traveling across the wild West bringing the news of the world to local
townspeople, agrees to help rescue a young girl who was kidnapped.
Captain Jefferson Kyle Kidd, played by Tom Hanks.
Johanna Leonberger, played by Helena Zengel.
Almay, played by Michael Angelo Covino.
Simon Boudlin, played by Ray McKinnon.
Doris Boudlin, played by Mare Winningham.
Mrs. Gannett, played by Elizabeth Marvel.
News of the World is a 2020 American Western film  co-written and directed by Paul Greengrass, based on the 2016 novel of the
same name by Paulette Jiles, and starring Tom Hanks and introducing Helena Zengel in her international film debut.
The film follows an aging Civil War veteran who must return a young girl who was taken in
by the Kiowa, and raised as one of them, to her last remaining family.
News of the World was released theatrically by Universal Pictures in the
United States on December 25, 2020, and grossed $12 million.
Internationally, the film was released by Netflix in
other territories on February 10, 2021.
It received positive reviews from critics, who praised the performances of Hanks and Zengel,
as well as the cinematography, musical score, and Greengrass's direction.
At the 93rd Academy Awards, the film received nominations for Best Original
Score, Best Cinematography, Best Production Design, and Best Sound.
Zengel received nominations for Best Supporting Actress at the
Golden Globes and Screen Actors Guild Awards.
The film explores themes of newspaper, based on novel
or book, texas, horse, native american.
The tone is emotional.